[ THUNDER CRASHING ]
PILOT : Uh , good evening , ladies and gentlemen . This is your pilot .
Uh , you 'll notice the " fasten seatbelt " sign is on .
We 're passing through a bit of turbulence here .
Unfortunately , we can 't get up over it and , uh , we can 't get underneath it .
Just hang in there . We 'll get through this as soon as we can .
Excuse me , miss .
Oh !
- Yes ? - Can I have a different seat , please ?
No , I 'm afraid we 're full tonight , sir . You 're gonna have to stay put .
Thanks , anyway .
[ GROANING ]
He 's going to make you help him ...
because you 're the last .
[ BELL RINGS ]
JOHN : Listen ...
I really need to change this seat .
I 'm sorry . There 's nothing I can do .
I 'm afraid of heights .
Don 't be a pussy .
WOMAN : Whoa !
It 's not fair ! I was almost out !
[ SCREAMING ]
[ GASPS ]
Shit .
[ FREDDY CACKLING ]
I 'll get you , my pretty , and your little soul too .
[ LAUGHING ]
[ JOHN GRUNTS ]
[ JOHN GROANING ]
[ SHOUTING ]
[ GRUNTING ]
God .
Whoa !
Oh , God .
One ticket ...
round trip .
Hurry up , boy .
You don 't wanna miss the bus .
[ LAUGHING MANIACALLY ]
[ BUS HORN HONKING ]
[ SCREAMING ]
[ LAUGHING ]
Oh . No screaming while the bus is in motion .
JOHN : Goddamn it .
[ JOHN SCREAMING ]
[ LAUGHING ]
Now be a good little doggie and go fetch .
Spencer , I wanna make sure that you understand our situation .
In one week , you walk out of here .
And I expect to see some changes in your behavior when you get home .
I know you 're hearing me . I put you in here because you gave me no choice .
- Next time , I 'll leave you here and walk away . - Thanks for the visit , Dad .
Nice job on my kid . I expected to see some improvement .
He isn 't a Toyota .
What a jerk .
[ SIGHS ]
- You okay ? - Yeah .
Dad came by to lay down some ground rules for when I come home .
No more running away , no more setting his cars on fire .
There are ways to get attention besides blowing up the garage .
Yeah , he barely even blinked .
All he wants me to do now is grow up to be him .
An exact copy .
I don 't feel like playing football and date-raping coeds .
One of these days , you 'll have to face your father .
KELLY : Maggie .
Look what I found in Spencer 's room .
MAGGIE : A pipe bomb , huh ?
Uh , that ? Well , I was just showing the kids some survival techniques .
[ SIGHS ]
I 've been confiscating stuff like this all week .
Where do they get it ?
Put this downstairs with the rest of the arsenal .
MAGGIE : The police were to dispose of it . - Police are supposed to do a lot of things .
MAN : Stop . Come back here .
- TRACY : Take your hands off me ! - Tracy .
- What 's the problem ? - She was beating on one of the kids .
- He was trying to hit on me . - She doesn 't like to be touched .
We have a session today , yes ?
I have Doc 's class .
Work around him .
I 'm sorry , sir .
MAN : You seen this junkie before ?
No , he 's new .
MAN : Beautiful . Another afternoon shot doing juvie paperwork .
Screw that shit .
Let 's just scoop him up and take him to the shelter .
Let the bleeding hearts do the typing .
[ TRACY GRUNTING ]
That 's it . Come on , Tracy .
That 's it . Oh , yeah , she 's bad .
The crowd loves her .
She 's getting ready for the heavyweight champion boxing match of the world .
Hey , hey , hey , look at her go . You know , you are sexy when you sweat .
[ LAUGHING ]
You ain 't getting none , Carlos . You ain 't getting none .
- You wouldn 't hit a guy with a handicap . - You call it a handicap ?
I call it chicken , man . Come on , let 's spar .
- Come on , you yellow-bellied ... Come on . - Forget it , Trace . I 'm ...
[ INAUDIBLE DIALOGUE ]
Don 't tune out . Why don 't you talk back to her ?
Like you talk back to your father ? Let me tell you something , Spence .
I stopped talking back when it became hazardous to my health . You know what I mean ?
- So are we set ? - Yeah , no problem .
I gave the driver our cash . As long as we do it before dawn , we 're free .
All right , that means we 're gonna be living large in Cali before the week is out .
You better be sure , man .
Trust me . I got all the bases covered . I need to get out of here more than you do .
You don 't know shit about needing to get out .
Your family 's a picnic , rich boy .
You think I hang around with you morons by choice ?
Your father didn 't try to set you up with his girlfriend 's older sister .
Don 't talk to me about fathers .
Yours come to visit too ?
Yeah , every time I close my eyes .
[ DOC HUMMING ]
All right , that did it . Yep . Okay .
They caught one of your star pupils beating up on one of our kids again .
- Tracy ? - You said you were making progress .
I only get 23 minutes a week with these kids .
With that kind of attention , we 're lucky she didn 't kill him .
[ SCOFFS ]
Ha , ha . Oh , that 's a good attitude for a therapist .
You know , Tracy 's got some deep trauma buried inside of her head .
Conventional therapy is not going to work .
And dream therapy is , huh ? You 're such a hippie .
You know , I can reach these kids through their dreams .
Give me a chance , I can help with your little problem .
I don 't have a little problem .
I just have a little reoccurring dream and I 'm handling it fine .
And you are not being paid to be a dream doctor .
I 'm barely being paid . That 's why I gotta do what I think is right .
- This is new . - You like it ?
These are ancient dream demons .
Supposedly , they roam the dreams of the living ...
till they find the most evil , twisted human imaginable .
Then they give him the power to cross the line ...
and turn our nightmares into reality .
[ KNOCKING ON DOOR ]
Maggie , cops just brought in another kid .
Real mess . Hasn 't slept for days , bad case of amnesia .
They need your evaluation right away .
MAGGIE : How long have you been awake ? JOHN : As far as I can remember .
I don 't know . About three days .
Looks more like three weeks .
Yeah , well , that 's the wonder of amnesia .
Just always keeps you guessing .
Where are you from ?
I don 't know !
All I know is that wherever I 'm from , I was the last .
- The last what ? - Survivor .
Look , do you have any , um , caffeine pills or coffee , maybe some Coke ?
I meant the soda .
Sit down .
- Why do you wanna stay awake ? - Because if I fall asleep ...
I 'm not waking up .
- Why do you think that ? - I don 't think it .
I feel it .
If I fall asleep , there 's gonna be trouble .
MAGGIE : " Springwood . "
Water tower .
JOHN [ SINGING ] : Four thousand , five hundred
And sixty-seven bottles Of beer on the wall
Four thousand , five hundred sixty-seven Bottles of beer
If one of those bottles Should happen to fall
What a case of ...
BOY : Hell , I 'll break a bottle over your head if you don 't shut the fuck up !
Four thousand , five hundred and sixty-six Bottles of beer on the wall
I won 't tell .
MAN : Now you 're it . Remember what you have to do .
You gotta tag me .
That 's a girl .
Over here . Come on .
Come to Daddy .
[ WOMAN SCREAMING ]
Play with me .
Tell me who I am .
I won 't tell .
Free me , you idiot ! I 'm your fucking memory !
[ SCREAMS ]
Oh , shit .
Asshole .
What were you dreaming about ?
A room .
A house .
A little girl .
Something about , uh , the town from my article .
I remember a water tower .
Um ...
The article , do you remember where you got it ?
- No . - The little girl , what did she look like ?
- Brown hair with red ribbons . - Red ribbons .
I don 't like it . There 's some connection between your dreams and his dreams ...
and his dreams mean bad news .
You think I 'm crazy , but I can feel it .
Why can 't anybody talk about anything but dreams around here ?
- I 'm sick of hearing about this bullshit . - You don 't believe that .
You think you can solve this puzzle , it can help with yours .
I don 't have a puzzle .
Yes , you do . And although you think you know everything ...
you may not be ready to face what this boy is gonna show you .
- I never said I wanted to go back there . - I 've dealt with amnesiacs before .
Taking you to Springwood is gonna trigger some spark to help you remember .
I don 't need a spark to help me to remember that it was a bad place .
You want a spark , you go . I 'll stay here , sparkless but happy .
I 'll be right there with you . Don 't worry .
Kelly , gonna take the van for a little while .
I told you not to let me fall asleep . Is that too much to ask for ?
- Go back . - Oh , my God . Pull over .
John . John , wake up .
[ BOTH SHOUTING ]
- Shit . - Oh , great .
Funny meeting you here .
Well , nice driving .
What the hell are you guys doing here ?
Great plan , asshole .
- It almost worked . MAGGIE : I can 't believe you people .
Pulling a stunt like that .
Oh , my God .
Look , the first thing we have to do is find a telephone .
You call Kelly and tell him where you are , understand ?
And then we have to figure out how to get you home .
Are you listening ?
Don 't scream at me .
- It was your driving that almost killed us . - Yeah .
[ CARNIVAL MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS ]
Two . Two for a dollar , right here .
Get them here . Here you go . Two for a dollar .
All right . First I want you to find a phone , call Kelly and tell him you 're all right .
I want you to get in that van and drive straight back to the shelter .
Think you can handle that , or do I have to call the police ?
- Get away from them . - You go away .
- " Or do I have to call the police ? " - Go away . Go away .
- She ain 't my mother . MAN 1 : There goes the bra .
MAN 2 : Who wants some peach cobbler here ? It 's not burned too bad .
You can just cut it right in the middle there .
[ MIMICKING ENGINE SOUND ]
MAN 3 : Step right up here . Right here . Here 's the place .
This is the place you wanna be here .
- There are no kids . - What ?
A town fair and there are no kids .
MAN 4 : Guys , look out .
MAN 5 : Guys , what the heck you doing over there ?
- What 's up , Spence ? - This phone 's out of order .
- So is this town . - You are not kidding .
Oh , what beautiful , adorable children . Would you like to come and live with us ?
It 's been so long since we 've had children in the house .
So long .
This time , I swear it 'll be different .
This time , I 'll be careful and I 'll hide you better so that he 'll never find you .
Lookie , I got your nose . Lookie .
Ethel .
I want my children back .
You know they bring him .
[ CHURCH BELL RINGING ]
Now , see what you done did ?
Jesus .
- We 're in Twin Peaks here . - Definitely .
- Have we seen enough ? - Yeah .
Good .
All right . Come on , back in the van .
- You know , that 's a very good idea . MAGGIE : Now . Go !
I hope they make it .
Let 's see what they can tell us at the school .
- What ? - Somebody rang those bells .
Lucky us .
CARLOS : Trace , there 's a map back here .
Did I say I needed a map ?
I can 't get over the way those people were looking at us .
Yeah , that was weird .
TRACY : Shit .
SPENCER : Nice going .
It takes talent to travel in a complete circle .
And you 're making me dizzy .
Jeez .
Do you have to do that ?
You 're such a heigh-ho , you know that ?
I don 't play that shit . I need all the senses I got .
Put that fucking thing out . It 's hard enough staying awake ...
- without you lighting up every 10 seconds . - This relaxes me .
I can relax you with these two fingers . I 'll just puncture your heart .
Mess up these seats .
You need to get laid .
Would you like the map now ?
- No , I don 't need any map . - Okay .
No , of course not .
- Why 'd you stop ? - Look .
SPENCER : Oh , great .
Give me the map .
Not a word .
Carlos , I asked you for the map .
What is this ? Hey .
Carlos . I asked you for the map .
What ?
Yeah , well , the map says we 're fucked .
Okay , look , you 've had two chances . Now it 's my turn .
- Dickhead . - Nice .
You will all be expected to pass both a written and an oral examination .
Don 't disturb him .
You will need to study this .
We 've got to get the dates right . If they get out of order , we get very confused .
John .
- You were here . - What ?
Welcome ...
to Freddy 101 .
Fourteen hundred and ninety-three Freddy sailed across the sea
[ CHUCKLES ]
These dates , they 're all within a 10-year period . What the hell happened here ?
JOHN : Freddy happened here .
Here 's a crucial point .
Anybody know what I 'm getting at ?
Anybody ? Come on , people .
We covered this . This is where they took away his child .
What child ?
Taken away , put in the town orphanage .
Freddy had a kid .
Fourteen hundred and ninety-four
Freddy came back to look for more
- There 's no way out . - Not with you driving .
- Yeah , well , you didn 't do much better . - No , but at least I did it in half the time .
- Come on , where are you going ? - Away .
We 're too fried to see straight . Let 's just find Maggie .
I 'm not turning myself over for any adult supervision .
This girl 's getting some rest .
In fact , I think I see my kind of neighborhood up ahead : empty .
You know , she 's losing it .
- The sad thing is I 'm starting to like her . - That is sad .
Come on , Trace , wait up .
This is the one . We 'll have it all to ourselves .
SPENCER : Bet there 's no heat . CARLOS : No plumbing , right ?
You 'll survive .
Come on .
[ TRACY SHOUTS ]
- Where you going ? - Gonna go upstairs and find a bed .
Man , I 'm tired .
I gotta find a bathroom .
Jeez , this place makes the shelter look like The Ritz .
Icky . Yuck .
[ SIGHS ]
Great . Well ...
[ CHUCKLES ]
At least it beats the streets , right , Carlos ?
Oh , this is good .
I 'm gonna get some sleep ...
and I will get us out of here in the morning . That 's right .
Jeez .
Why do you think that kid said not to fall asleep ?
Because he 's a lame-o freak .
Miss Maggie 's pet psycho .
Carlos ! Carlos !
Carlos !
Tracy ?
- TRACY : Carlos ! - Tracy ?
- TRACY : Carlos ? - Tracy ?
TRACY : Where the hell are you ? Why aren 't you listening to me , Carlos ?
- Damn , the door 's sticking again . MAN 1 : No , I ain 't giving you a damn bottle .
MAN 2 : Is it ready ? MAN 1 : I 'm gonna pour it all out .
CARLOS : Tracy ?
Tracy ? Ugh !
Tracy , where are you ?
WOMAN : Behind you .
Mama ?
Mama .
[ GRUNTS ]
Maybe you don 't hear so good .
Maybe I clean out your ears for you .
No , no , Mama , please . I 've been a good boy . You don ...
You don 't understand . I 've been good , Mama .
Please , don 't make me deaf , Mama . Please .
- I 'm sorry . - I 'm not .
[ SCREAMING ]
Oh , Carlos , lend me your ear .
No !
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ THUNDER CRASHING ]
Give me my hearing back !
Yes .
[ SCREAMING ]
Where is it ?
[ CHUCKLES ]
No . No .
Shh .
[ GROANS ]
You wouldn 't do that , would you , man ?
No , no , no . Please . No , man .
[ CHUCKLES ]
Ah .
Ooh .
No , no , no .
No , no . No , please . No , no .
No .
[ SCREECHING ]
No . No , no , no . No .
[ SCREAMING ]
Nice hearing from you , Carlos . Ha , ha .
TRACY : Carlos ?
Carlos .
I can 't find Carlos .
You see what 's on this TV ?
[ SCOFFS ]
I gotta take the van . I 'm gonna look for him .
[ MEN GROANING ON TV ]
CARLOS [ ON TV ] : Give me some room .
Spence ! Spencer !
Don 't fall asleep , man ! Get out !
Spencer , get out , man !
Carlos , man .
We were just looking for you .
CARLOS : Spence ! Spencer ! Don 't fall asleep , man !
Spencer , you stupid stoner !
We shouldn 't even be here .
We 're supposed to be finding out about you , not some dead killer 's kid .
We might be talking about the same thing .
Look , the whole town is obsessing on this Krueger character .
Don 't you start .
But why else would they be afraid of me ?
Why else am I still alive when everybody else is dead ?
[ SINGING ] Skip , skip , skip to my Lou
Skip to my Lou , my darlin '
Skip , skip , skip to my Lou
Martha , no running . Everyone , hold hands .
[ SINGING ] Skip , skip , skip to my Lou
Oh , you 've come back . How nice .
Do you remember me ?
Well , of course , I do , my boy . I remember every one of my children .
Especially you .
What a pretty little girl you were .
And I remember you and you .
- Do you remember the Krueger child ? - Ha , ha . Of course .
Who was it ?
We 're not permitted to disclose a child 's real identity .
Oh , Melissa . Melissa . You must let Bobby have the ball .
- John . - GIBBONS : Come here . Come on .
That 's all right . You share .
I wonder who has a little bare footie around here . Let me see .
K. Krueger ? Could mean anything from Kevin to Kyle .
MAGGIE : All it really means is there was a child here by that name .
JOHN : No .
It 's me . Ha , ha .
GIBBONS : Yes . Oh , look ...
I 'm his kid .
That 's why he 's kept me alive .
He 's trying to play some sick game with me .
He is dead , all right ? He 's dead and you 're not his kid .
How do you know ?
She remembered me .
MAGGIE : She remembered me too and 50 other imaginary friends .
Let 's get out of here .
GIBBONS : Let 's draw a picture . We haven 't drawn a picture all day .
There you go . Clippety-clop , clippety-clop . Isn 't that fun ?
[ TIRES SQUEALING ]
- TRACY : Maggie . - Tracy .
- I can 't believe I found you . - What are you still doing here ?
I can 't find Carlos and Spencer 's wasted at this old house and ...
We gotta get to them before Freddy does .
- No . - Who 's Freddy ?
- I 'll tell you on the way . Come on ! - Yeah . All right .
Goddamn it .
[ TV HUMMING ]
[ SIGHS ]
All right , once again .
This is your brain .
This is your brain on drugs .
Questions ?
Yeah . What are you on ?
Looks like a frying pan and some eggs to me .
[ FREDDY LAUGHING ]
Hey , Spence , let 's trip out .
[ IRON BUTTERFLY 'S "
IN-A-GADDA-DA-VIDA " PLAYING ON TV ]
Oh , cool .
- In-A-Gadda-Da-Vida , honey . - Whoa !
Don 't you know that I love you
In-A-Gadda-Da-Vida , baby
Don 't you know that I 'll always be true
Now he 's gone .
JOHN : He must 've fallen asleep . - Look here and upstairs .
- I 'm gonna look downstairs . - They 're not here anymore .
Just humor me , will you , please ? And look .
Where am I ?
FREDDY : Jump , boy .
Whoa !
FREDDY : Jump .
SPENCER : Whoa !
- Dad ? - Be like me .
Be like me . Be like me .
Father knows best .
SPENCER : Oh , stop .
[ SPENCER GRUNTING ]
I 'm not like you . I don 't wanna be like you .
I 'm not like you .
Be like me .
Now I 'm playing with power .
[ SPENCER GRUNTING ]
All right .
Super Spencer . Yeah .
Hey , great graphics .
Whoa , I 'm here .
Carlos ?
Yeah .
I found Spencer !
Okay . Hold him down .
Oh , shit .
- Hold on . Hold on . - Jesus Christ . Hold on .
- What 's happening ? - He 's stuck in a nightmare .
- It 's kicking the shit out of him . MAGGIE : Well , wake him up .
- TRACY : He 's too wasted . - MAGGIE : Spencer . Jesus .
It 's Freddy .
- MAGGIE : Get him out . - Hold him .
I 'll go into his dream , try and bring him out before he gets killed .
- TRACY : Come on . Hold him . - That 's crazy .
Well , what do you call that , rational ?
Right , left . Right , left . Right , left .
- He 's getting trashed . - I have to go in .
What about Freddy ?
Freddy won 't hurt me . I 'm family .
Okay , so how are you gonna go in ?
Well ...
you 're gonna have to lay me out .
- What is ... ? - Come on , just fucking lay me out !
Wait a second . Doc told me a different way .
There 's no time to talk . Just do it !
Jesus Christ .
I told you I knew an easier way .
" Concentration and meditation . " That 's what Doc always says .
This place is incredible .
Ha , ha . Pow ! Bam !
- Splat . - Is that him ?
Jump , boy .
Oh , shit . Spencer .
TRACY : Come on , John . Let go of me . Let go .
JOHN : Get out of here . Now , Tracy . Now .
Hey , you forgot the Power Glove .
No ! Bastard !
Pow !
Boing . Boing .
Boing , boing , boing , boing !
VIDEO GAME DADS : Be like me . Be like me . Be like me .
Spencer , do ...
[ SPENCER GRUNTING ]
[ SCREAMING ]
What do you know ? I beat my high score .
[ LAUGHING ]
Oh , yeah .
Great to be back in business .
Thanks to you .
[ SCREAMING ]
Oh !
Daddy 's waiting for you , little girl .
Shut the fuck up , man .
Tracy .
Spencer 's gone . I couldn 't stop it .
John 's still in there .
I couldn 't wake him up .
Come on , snap out of it ! What are we gonna do ?
We 're gonna pick him up and we 're gonna get the hell out of here .
[ SCREAMS ]
Phew .
[ SCREAMING ]
[ GASPS ]
Not again .
He 's not gonna get me again .
Nothing is gonna make me get off this bed .
Damn it .
I hate this house .
[ SCREAMING ]
[ SHOUTS ]
[ GASPS ]
[ TIRES SQUEALING ]
FREDDY : Johnny .
Up here .
[ FREDDY LAUGHING ]
I know why you let me go .
Oh , do you think I 'm your daddy ?
Mm-mm .
Wrong .
[ FREDDY LAUGHING ]
Uh-oh . Oh !
But you let me live .
Only long enough for you to bring me back my daughter .
JOHN : Your daughter ?
And now she 's gonna take me to a whole new playground .
No !
Grounded !
[ SCREAMING ]
John !
TRACY : Oh , my God , Maggie . What 's going on ?
Come on , Maggie . Let 's go .
[ JOHN GROANING ]
TRACY : Let 's get out of here . Let 's get the hell out of here .
It 's ... It 's not a boy .
It 's ...
TRACY : Come on . We gotta get out of here . Now . Come on .
Come on , Maggie . Let 's go .
Come on , let 's go now !
You forgot where you came from , kid ...
but I know where you 're going . Ha , ha .
It 's traveling time .
[ SHOUTING ]
TRACY : Maggie .
What 's wro ... ? Maggie , get in the van . Come on .
Come on , get in the van ! We gotta get the hell out of here !
Oh , God .
TRACY : Let 's go .
[ TIRES SQUEALING ]
Whatever happened , it wasn 't your fault .
MAN 1 : I wasn 't even there , man . MAN 2 : It 's gonna happen again .
MAGGIE : Carlos , Tracy , and Spencer stowed away in the back of the shelter van .
They were trying to escape . Can you believe it ?
So I took them to the phone . They were supposed to call you .
John Doe and I were gonna check out the school .
But Tracy got separated .
- And then they ran away . - What the hell are you talking about ?
I 'm talking about Carlos and Spencer and the John Doe .
Kelly , they just disappeared .
You 've been handling too many cases , Maggie . Those kids were never here .
I would remember any new arrival .
Kelly , I 'm talking about 48 hours ago . I brought you a John Doe .
You don 't remember ? You 're the one who 's handling too many cases .
Get some rest , Maggie .
And then , um ...
we got back and no one remembers John or Carlos .
It 's like they never existed .
I 've been hearing strange shit .
Like some of the kids are dreaming about Carlos .
And they don 't even remember him .
I remember him .
Why ?
Because I can control my dreams . I 'm not fooled by this thing you saw .
- Freddy . - DOC : Whatever he is ...
he 's fucking with the line between dreams and reality .
He didn 't just kill Carlos and the others .
He erased them .
[ SOBBING ]
JOHN : It 's not a boy . It 's not a boy . It 's not a boy .
Mother !
Mother .
[ GRUNTING ]
[ LAUGHING ]
Shit .
- You 're getting ready to kill somebody . - Defend myself .
It 's your mind he 'll go for .
Your fear .
Oh , I knew it , I knew it , I knew it .
Maggie ? What are you doing ?
Who are they ?
- Let me have that . - I have to know .
I don 't know . I don 't know who they were . They wouldn 't tell me .
They have rules about no contact .
Oh , there 's been contact .
[ YOUNG MAGGIE GIGGLING ]
FREDDY : You 're it . You 're it .
Come to Daddy .
[ LORETTA SCREAMING ]
I won 't tell .
Oh , God .
Fred , please .
I won 't tell .
We need to talk , Loretta .
Go inside , honey .
LORETTA : Oh , I won 't tell .
- I told you never to go near my things . - Oh , I didn 't mean to , Fred , I ...
Right ? Isn 't that right ?
Right .
Stop .
Katherine .
You were such a little artist .
No , it can 't be .
I know who I am .
You 're my blood .
Only you could have brought me out , in your mind .
But you can 't be my father .
They took you away from me , but I made them pay .
I took all their children away from them .
And now ...
that 's over .
Come on .
The shelter .
Time to start all over again .
But this isn 't Springwood .
[ CHUCKLES ]
Every town has an Elm Street .
[ LAUGHING MANIACALLY ]
Tracy .
[ GASPS ]
MAN : Is it ready ?
Tracy , girl .
Daddy 's home .
Daddy , you 're dead .
MAN : I 'm home , darling .
Come say hello .
I don 't want to , Daddy .
Come on . Give Daddy some honey .
No one has to know .
You 're not my daddy . You 're not my daddy !
MAN : Come on , Tracy .
Here !
Do you love me now ? !
Do you love me now ? ! Come on !
[ SHOUTS ]
He 's dead .
My daddy 's dead .
He 's DEA ...
[ GROANS ]
No honey for Daddy ?
[ FREDDY LAUGHING ]
What 's with kids today , huh ?
No respect .
You can 't scare me anymore .
Oh , you better speak up .
Oh , must be my deaf ear .
[ LAUGHING ]
[ BOTH GRUNTING ]
Kung fu this , bitch .
This is my dream and I do what I want .
It might be your dream , but it 's my rules .
[ SCREAMING ]
Doc . I need to talk to Doc .
- Okay . - Come on !
Tracy ?
TRACY : Doc . Doc , is that you ? - Yeah , Tracy , where are you ?
TRACY : I 'm over here in one of the lockers . You gotta get me out .
- Where the hell are you ? - TRACY : Right here .
[ AS TRACY ] You taught her a lot .
[ IN NORMAL VOICE ] But there 's so much more to learn .
How about this , Doc ?
[ LAUGHING ]
[ GRUNTING ]
Sticks and stones may break my bones ...
but nothing will ever kill me .
Well , let 's see now .
First they tried burning me . Ha , Ha .
Then they tried burying me .
[ LAUGHING ]
But this , this is my favorite .
They even tried holy water .
[ LAUGHING ]
But I just keep on ticking .
Because they promised me that .
- They ? - The dream people .
The ones that gave me this job .
In dreams ...
I am forever .
Too bad you 're not .
[ WATCH ALARM BEEPING ]
[ MACHINE BUZZING ]
Doc .
Thank God .
I think I 've got a way to get him .
TRACY : So , what 's the plan , Doc ?
- Thanks . - DOC : You can 't get him in a dream .
But if this can come out , he can come out .
And if he can come out , he can bleed .
- And die . - DOC : Right .
How will you know when I got him ?
I 'm gonna find you with this and then I 'm bringing you out .
Now , you 've got to be holding him to carry him out .
I know .
Now , he 's gonna try and trick you like he tricked Tracy .
And he 's gonna try to use your eyes to fool you . You 'll use these .
- Get the hell out of here . - You wanna live ?
These mean nothing here .
But in the dream , they can be anything you want .
He got inside of your head , you get inside of his .
That 's my job , isn 't it ?
Be careful . He 's good at finding out what hurts the most .
DOC : Exactly . - That 's why you gotta take me with you .
I can 't .
It 's gotta be me and him .
All right , Doc .
Put me in .
Strap her in .
Okay .
Take a deep breath .
- Okay . - Good .
Ten ...
nine ...
eight ...
seven , six ...
five , four ...
three , two ...
one .
MAGGIE : And get inside his brain .
[ SHOUTING ]
[ SHOUTING AND LAUGHING ]
I 'm in his memories .
[ CHANTING ] Son of a hundred maniacs Son of a hundred maniacs
Oh , yeah . Ha , ha .
MAN : Freddy .
Freddy .
You ready for it , boy ?
You 've been a waste since the day I took you in .
Now it 's time to take your medicine .
[ LAUGHING ]
Thank you , sir .
May I have another ?
[ LAUGHING ]
You wanna know the secret of pain ?
If you just stop feeling it , you could start using it .
CROWD : Child murderer ! Beast !
Kill him !
Freddy .
We know what you want .
- FREDDY : I want it all ! - Of course you do .
- Then open up . - And you shall be forever .
[ FREDDY SCREAMS ]
[ LORETTA SHOUTING ]
[ FREDDY GRUNTING ]
Mommy .
[ CRYING ]
Don 't worry , baby .
Mommy just had to take her medicine for snooping in Daddy 's special work .
But you won 't tell , will you ?
I won 't tell .
But you did tell , didn 't you ? Ha , ha .
And now it 's time to take your medicine .
[ LAUGHING ]
You killed my mother !
She 's got him .
Let 's get her out of there .
[ SCREAMING ]
I 've got you .
I had him .
Where the hell is he ?
- Maybe the trip killed him . - No .
Because I 'm still seeing things the way I did in my dream .
It 's not over . Let 's go .
DOC : Cops were supposed to pick this stuff up .
Be glad they didn 't . We 're gonna have to hit him with everything we 've got .
Whoa !
Check out this knife .
- Hey , put that away . - MAGGIE : That 's too small .
Guess so .
DOC : You sure that 's big enough ?
- Still believe he 's gonna show up , huh ? - Yep .
Come on , Tracy . Over here .
I can feel it .
- You 're real here . - FREDDY : It wasn 't my fault .
It wasn 't .
You saw what they did to me when I was a kid .
You saw .
I loved you ...
and your mother .
I tried so hard to be good .
I know , Daddy .
But when they took you from me , it wasn 't right .
Oh , I knew you 'd believe me .
Come to Daddy .
[ SCREAMS ]
Maggie .
Over here .
I 'm okay .
Maggie , watch out .
- Where 's the key ? - I don 't know .
The lock 's jammed .
I didn 't need a glove to kill your bitch of a mother ...
and I don 't need one now .
[ GASPING ]
Come on . Let go .
Come on , let go .
- No ! No ! - No ! Get down .
I 'll show you how .
Like you showed my mother and Carlos ?
And Spencer ?
- Give Daddy the glove back , princess . - Never .
Give it to me .
Give it to me . Give me that glove .
Give me the glove .
In your dreams .
[ BOTH SHOUTING AND GRUNTING ]
Oh , Daddy .
I remember when we used to hold hands together when I was a kid .
- I didn 't like it then either . - Aah !
I forgot how much it hurts to be human .
[ MAGGIE GROANING AND FREDDY LAUGHING ]
Maggie .
[ SHOUTING ]
What ... ?
Come on .
Oh , you ...
[ FREDDY SCREAMING ]
Go ahead .
Put it on .
It 's in your blood .
That 's it , put it on .
Feels good , doesn 't it ?
Yeah . Come on .
Let your daddy show you how to use it .
[ SCREAMING ]
Maggie ! Maggie !
Happy Father 's Day .
TRACY : Come on , Doc .
Come on . Yeah .
Come on , let 's hurry . Let 's get out of here . Come on .
[ GASPS ]
Kids .
[ SCREAMING ]
- You all right ? - Yeah , I 'm okay .
[ CHUCKLES ]
Freddy 's dead .
[ INAUDIBLE DIALOGUE ]
[ English - US - SDH ]